6 years ago, I was taken
from prison and forced
to become an assassin for a
secret unit of the government...
a black ops program called
division that has now gone rogue.
They destroyed my identity,
and they destroyed
the man I loved.
I escaped. And now the man that
trained me... someone I trusted...
is hunting me.
What division doesn't know is that I
have a partner on the inside, Alex.
A new recruit with a dark past, who I've
trained in secret to resist their control.
Together, we're going to take
division apart one mission at a time.
And the last word they'll breathe
before the end will be my name...
An I.D. on the target yet?
Jill Morelli.
She's a freelance reporter.
28 years old.
Also runs a blog that tracks
governments conspiracies. Awkward.
How did she get wind of our op?
Who talked to her?
We're not sure.
I hacked into her home PC.
There's no mention
of the op in there.
But she knows we were
at the crash site.
The girl's cracked
some major scandals.
But she's attracted
just as many libel suits.
Most of the major papers
won't touch her.
It only takes one, right?
Agent Donegan, use grab team B.
I want to find out
exactly what she knows
and how she came to know it.
Donegan, I'll get you the
coordinates for the target.
This is the operations room.
The window looks out
into the training area
so the all-mighty parents
can look down on the kids.
Most of their key intel
passes through that hub.
When a new target comes in, operations
becomes the most popular club in town.
If we're going
to sabotage division,
that's one of the veins I'm
going to need you to tap.
Doesn't the window
work both ways?
Gold star.
The glass is tinted.
So, you're going to have to get close.
The problem is,
you can't just walk up
and press your nose against it
like a kid in a candy store.
Jaden.
I'm just looking
for a sparring partner.
Find someone else, newbie.
You and I are supposed
to play nice.
Oh, I forgot.
We're still on probation
because of the whole
you attacking me thing.
I got nothin'
to say about that.
There's something
about me you should know.
Aah!
Man: Go break it up!
[Buzzing]
Computer: Target name
is Jill Morelli.
Check it out.
Yeah. I'm out of the elevator.
Say again?
I don't know.
15-20 minutes?
Yeah. It'll be fine, honey.
Just reheat it when I get home.
No. No. I'm in the garage now.
Yeah. I'm losing you.
Jeremy!
Damnit!
Morelli, you scared
the hell out of me!
Oh, sorry, Jer. But I'm sitting
on the story of the year here.
And Joanne won't put
my calls through to you.
I just need 2 minutes.
You got 10 seconds
till I get to my car.
It's about air America flight
that crashed in the
Appalachian mountains.
112 dead. No survivors.
Every paper in the country
is covering that story.
Yeah? Which one's got
the exclusive
on the black helicopters?
What black helicopters, Jill?
The ones my source saw
land at the crash site
before the huge forest fire conveniently
burned up all the evidence.
Evidence of what?
Exactly. When I called
Air America for comment,
they put me on hold.
And guess who picked up the line.
Henry Sampson.
You spoke to Henry Sampson?
Yeah. Since when does
a CEO of a major airline
pick up the phone to talk
to a freelance journo?
When he's scared, Jeremy.
When he's scared.
Ohh...
What? Story of the year,
Jeremy!
I've heard that before.
My source has video
of the crash site.
Yeah? How much does
your source want this time?
50 grand. But how can you
put a price to the truth?
We're not TMZ, Jill.
We don't pay for stories.
Even if it is
the story of the year.
[Silenced gunshot] [gasp]
[Tires squealing]
[Muffled screams]
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
You just killed him.
And you're going to prison
for the rest of your life,
unless we get that video.
Aah!
No!
[Tires squealing]
Gold star.
I don't know. Set up a candlelight
vigil or something like that.
That should keep them off
our back for 5 minutes.
[Door opens]
Mr. Sampson?
The gentleman to see you, sir.
Your baggage claim check, sir.
It's not funny, Percy.
Relax, Henry. You'll survive.
And more importantly,
so will your airline.
Read and interesting article
in "The Post" this morning.
Apparently their chief editor
was shot dead last night.
Hmm.
I paid you to keep this quiet.
No, you paid me to clean up
after your plane crash
and collect the cargo.
I did that.
And somebody saw you doing it.
Somebody who had
a video camera.
Somebody who called a reporter
who then called me asking
about black helicopters.
I'll locate
and destroy the video.
No extra charge.
And the reporter?
You mean the unhinged,
unemployed maniac
who shot her boss?
We'll get her back.
Although in the future,
I would advise you to keep
our dealings private.
[Scoff] Excuse me?
Last night's incident was the
result of third party interference.
A third party who
more than likely
was informed by a leak
from within your company.
Percy, if there's a leak,
it's not coming from my shop.
It's coming from yours.
[Footsteps approaching]
Don't get up too fast.
DMPH takes a while to wear off.
It's the worst.
I got you some java.
[Gasp]
Jill, if I were going
to hurt you,
I would have done it already.
You're at my place.
They're not going to find you here.
"They"? Who are they?
Who are you?
I'm Nikita. I used to be
one of them. I'm not anymore.
[Gasp]
Oh, I read your blog,
by the way,
all that crap in there about
illegal black ops,
assassination programs,
ghost agents...
I mean, you're on the right
track, in a general sense.
Your specifics are way off.
What?
Doesn't matter.
Nothing on your website would
make them want to kill you.
Were you working on a story
with that editor?
Ahh. Oh, Jeremy...
Oh, God, Jeremy.
Jill.
Oh.
The plane crash.
That's what we were talking about.
Those hit men wanted me
to give up my source.
Listen, it's going to be ok.
We're going to expose
what they're trying to hide.
But you have to tell me
what that is.
I don't know.
All right, I hacked
the state police server
and put out an APB
for Jill Morelli.
Got her wanted in connection
with the murder of her editor.
Just heard from the on-site team.
Target apartment secure.
No sign of Nikita.
Patch me through.
I listed Morelli
as armed and dangerous.
You wanna go federal?
What's the last
confirmed location?
Cell phone pinged off a tower
in Brooklyn at 1:07 am.
Nikita must have dumped it right
after you guys botched the job.
They could be a couple hundred
miles in any direction by now.
Widen the net.
Tri-state area.
On-site team on 3.
Any leads?
Man: There's a whole bunch
of material in here...
notepads, bulletin boards,
file cabinets.
Ok. Clean it out. Bring it here...
all of it... now.
Yes, sir.
Tell Percy I need to see him.
A couple of days ago this guy
contacted me through my site.
Said he had some video
that would blow my mind.
Air America crash,
2 helicopters,
some paramilitary operation.
He wouldn't give me specifics.
Made me drive out to Virginia
just to meet him.
Young guy.
Scared of what he saw,
not faking it.
Wanted $50,000
just to show me the video.
So, you went to "the
post" for the 50,000?
I was hoping for 5.
Maybe.
The guy's supposed to call me
at 1:00 pm tomorrow.
Wait. What day is this?
It's tomorrow.
What's your source's name?
I don't know.
He wouldn't tell me.
What's his number?
He has my number.
What... what happened
to my phone?
I took the battery
and the SIM card out
so they couldn't trace you.
You got a boyfriend?
Roommate?
No. Why?
Well, because those men are
definitely at your house by now.
Let's call the police.
Oh, no.
They control the police.
Right now they're doing everything
they can to hunt you down.
I thought you said they won't
be able to find me here.
You're not staying here.
You have a very important
phone call in...
42 minutes.
Percy: Nikita's making
good on her threat.
Third time she's interfered
with one of our missions.
That we know of.
What we do know is that
she's been ahead of us
at each step.
At a certain point
we have to consider
the possibility of
a leak from the inside.
A high level leak.
I'd like to rule out
a data breach
before we start a mole hunt.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Data breach?
No way. No.
Our network is Fort Knox.
Internal servers
are air gapped,
and I run routine tests
on the outer defenses.
We're talking
5-tier security
with protocols that rotate
every hour on the hour.
That's proprietary software.
Only person who could dream of
hacking into division is me.
What?
Well, you did have a prolonged
interaction with Nikita
directly following
her reappearance.
If by interaction you
mean kidnap and torture,
yeah, you debriefed me,
remember?
A debriefing
that Nikita allowed
by allowing you
to return to us.
Dude, she pistol-whipped
my face.
What are we even talking
about here?
Take him down to see Amanda.
I'll call and give her instructions.
What the hell is this?
I'm not the mole.
Well, then you have nothing
to worry about.
So, he calls me and I let it
go to voicemail, of course.
I can't even check it.
His voice reminds me of his face.
It's disgusting.
What part of "I don't like you"
does he not understand?
We have to check out that
new wine bar this weekend.
Ohh. I love
wine bars.
I know you do.
Whose office is this?
Don't know. It'll work.
Well, what if they come back
when we're in here?
Nobody's coming back.
It's lunchtime.
Your boy's going
to call in 2 minutes.
We've got 15 before we...
What are you doing?
I always eat when I'm nervous.
Jill, the second
I turn on this phone,
they're going
to know where we are.
I'm going to need you
to get your source
to agree to a trade
for the video fast.
What if he asks for the money?
You have it.
[Beep]
Ok. I've got a hit
on the target phone.
Getting its twenty
from the GPS.
It's either a trick or she
needs to receive a call.
Are we up the carrier?
Yeah. But it looks like they've
got call forwarding enabled.
She's talking to the source.
It's 1:05.
Where the hell is he?
I don't know.
[Buzzing]
[Phone rings]
Hello.
Man: Hey. It's me. How'd it
go with your editor?
Um, it was good.
I have the money.
What is it?
Is it cash? Check?
It's check.
I just need to know
who to write it out to.
Ok. Ok. I want you to take
a picture of the check
and upload it
to my flicker account.
This is Malia Watson, Jill's editor.
What in the world
is on this video?
And why in the world
would I pay you $50,000
for something that's probably
been mocked up on your desktop?
You know, you'll just have
to see it for yourself.
Honey, I don't have time
for games.
Better luck with
"the enquirer." Be well.
Wait. You have to understand.
I never meant to see this.
I was just hiking off the trail
when I heard the crash.
And... and I ran over, and when
I got there, it was just...
wreckage everywhere.
And... and I heard
these helicopters,
so I thought
it was search and rescue.
Are these the so-called
black helicopters?
Yeah. And the guys that repelled
out of them were like commandoes.
Instead of looking
for survivors,
they start hauling these
huge bags out of the wreck.
The bags were packed
with cocaine.
It was like the whole plane
was packed with coke
and these guys were just
grabbing it out.
How do you know it was cocaine?
It was either that or someone was
about to bake a really big cake.
Ok, kid. We have the money.
You have the video.
Where do you wanna meet
for the trade?
The quad at
north Virginia state, ok?
Tomorrow. 10:00 am.
Was that really necessary?!
Great spot to hide
from the trace.
Where do you want us to start?
Percy told me what's going on.
And I have to agree, there's
something off with your story.
I didn't do anything, Amanda.
Why don't you guys believe me?
I believe that you
believe that, Birkhoff.
[Scoffs] Great.
Psycho babble.
How much you charging for this session?
I only want you
to open up to me.
You can tell me anything.
No. No. No.
You are trying to get me to admit
to something that I didn't do.
What did you and Nikita talk
about when she captured you?
Oh, we've been over this
1,000 times.
She told me she wanted
to burn down division.
I told her she was insane.
And you and Nikita were
comrades when she served here.
Did you ever have
feelings for her?
You know what?
I'm getting a feeling right
now like I was kidnapped
and now I'm being framed
for giving her intel!
Birkhoff, I'm not holding it
against you.
If you have an emotional connection
to Nikita, it's perfectly natural.
Coworkers often develop physical and
emotional attractions for one another.
She was a recruit.
A super hot one, yeah.
But I know the rules.
Look, but don't touch.
She's not a recruit anymore.
Whose fault is that?
Ever since
she held you hostage,
Nikita has had access to highly
confidential information.
And if you had done your job,
Nikita would still be
serving us right now.
You see...
You're the one who screwed
the pooch, Amanda.
You were supposed to mold her into
this perfect, obedient Agent.
But the second girlfriend got a
chance to split, she took it.
Where you going?
Martin?
Oh.
Take him to medical.
Oh, come on.
I wanna run an FMRI
brain scan for lie detection.
I'm not lying.
Ok. All right.
Full body cavity search
as well.
That... that is overkill,
Amanda!
Ow! Ow! Amanda!
Tell me you found the video.
We're still looking
for the source.
I would like your permission
to enlist some of the recruits
to help with the trace.
We've emptied the reporter's apartment,
her public storage locker,
brought everything here.
I get it. Too much material
to sift through on the clock.
Fine. Do it.
I also would like to give them
the target's full profile.
Absolutely not.
Like you said,
we're on the clock.
Redacting intel
will only slow us down.
If we give them a full profile,
it will invariably prompt
the inane moral debate
about the target
being a good person.
Last thing we need right now is for another
recruit to discover their inner Nikita.
Tell them it's
a training exercise.
All right, listen up.
We're running a training exercise.
3-man units.
This will be a competition.
Team leaders, pick your people.
Jaden.
Alex.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to save your life.
Both of yours.
You guys were given an ultimatum
that came straight from operations.
Show visible improvement in the
next 2 weeks or get cancelled.
That was a week ago.
How do you think you're doing?
If anyone else here
fails this test,
they'll meal penalty or maybe
solitary at the worst.
If either of you fail,
you may not be coming back.
Good evening.
This exercise is designed to
test your tracking skills.
You'll be examining
evidence collected
from the home
of a domestic terrorist,
who was planning to meet
a munitions expert.
Now, their goal was to destroy
a government facility.
Your task is to uncover the
identity of the munitions expert
and where the meet
was going to take place.
Our agents were able
to do this in 12 hours.
Let's see if you can do better.
15 minutes, ok?
Then we're back in the car.
Got 90 miles to go,
and we gotta take back roads.
No more nervous appetite?
I keep seeing Jeremy's face.
He was starring
right at me when...
you didn't kill him, Jill.
They did.
And why?
For what? For money?
Yeah.
For a lot of money.
Think about it, ok.
Henry Sampson is using passenger
planes to smuggle drugs.
Probably to keep from going under
like all the other airline companies.
A real-life
story of the year.
Jeremy would have loved this.
Well, when we get this video, you're going
to make sure your article gets published.
Yeah.
If we get the video.
Those guys coming after us
aren't airline security.
They're the commando guys
from the crash site.
Who are they?
Come on! You said before I
was on the right track.
Some kind of government
black ops unit?
Maybe even mercenaries?
You need to stick
with what you can prove.
If this video turns out to be
what all it's cracked up to be,
you get to prove that a fortune
500 CEO is smuggling drugs.
You will never be able to prove who
the guys were in the helicopters.
Why?
Because they don't have decals on
their vehicles or their clothing.
Because there's no record
that they exist,
no documentation, no evidence.
What about you? You were part of them.
You're evidence.
I don't exist either.
Why won't you tell me
what you know?
Why are you protecting them?
I'm protecting you, Jill.
You don't think that if I could have
gone to the press to take them down,
I would have done it?
You won't be the first reporter
I've seen them kill.
Yeah. Well, I won't let
Jeremy die for nothing.
I have to tell
the whole story, Nikita.
I owe him at least that much.
We gotta go.
Now, get up. Put your head down.
Follow me.
Excuse me, miss?
Go! Go! Go!
We gotta lose the car.
They're gonna know
where we are.
But you just knocked them out!
I'm not talking about the cops.
[Tires squeal]
Got a hit on Nikita.
90 miles outside of Blacksburg off highway 81.
Still have the reporter
with her?
2 highway patrol officers
recognized Morelli
from the bulletin we sent out.
Nikita slipped the net.
Ahh. Amateurs.
Alpha team's en route
to Virginia.
We got a chopper there.
I wanna see this first.
Find out how she breached us.
It's you.
I'm not the mole, genius.
It's my molar.
Second bicuspid actually,
lower left.
I had medical
run an FMRI on Birkhoff.
Imagine my surprise when it showed
a tiny wireless transmitter
imbedded in his tooth.
Nikita must have planted it
there when he was passed out.
Possibly.
Possibly?
I think I'd remember that.
He passed the lie detection.
She had to remove the cap
in order to insert the bug.
You must have felt
that afterwards.
Oh, I felt it.
My whole face was sore for like a week
after she got done with me.
Why are you smiling?
Look. Just get it
out of there.
Get what out of where?
Amanda, I'm totally sorry
about that whole
"you're bad at your job" thing.
And I completely take it back.
Please.
Drugs, please.
[Door closes]
Describe him again.
Early twenties.
African American.
Kinda hipster cute.
Hipster cute?
Yeah, you know.
An ironic t-shirt kinda guy.
With the big jeans.
Hangs out in the coffee shops...
yeah. I get it.
You know, maybe we got
the location wrong.
Maybe he's waiting
for us somewhere else
and can't call us 'cause
you stomped on my phone.
We're at the right place.
He's just not going to show up.
Probably saw the news.
What news?
That you're wanted for murder.
He's paranoid.
Ok, what do we do now?
I mean, we're screwed.
We're going to track him
down ourselves. Come on.
These notebooks are just
conspiracy theory crap.
I mean, what are we supposed
to be looking for anyway?
Behavioral patterns,
motives, potential targets.
There's a bunch of stuff in here on a plane crash.
Maybe she caused it.
They said the terrorist was targeting
a government facility not a plane.
The Pentagon? A plane
crashed into that.
Yeah. And there's a conspiracy
theory on that in here, too.
Why are the names blacked out?
They don't want to
make it easy on us.
I do you know it's a she.
What?
The terrorist. What makes
you think its a woman?
Smell. Grapefruit
and vanilla-scented candles.
All right, show-off.
I'll see your scented candles,
and I'll raise you this.
Handwritten note.
Video on
A.T. Stony Creek.
Maybe a.T. Are the initials
of the munitions expert.
Stony Creek's in Virginia.
Plane crash was in Virginia.
A.T. could be
Appalachian trail.
Not bad.
All right, anything not tied to
Virginia moves off the table.
Let's get a map.
Where's the movie theater
you first met him at?
Right here.
He asked you to meet him at 2 different
locations near the university.
He was hiking the day of the
crash, which was a Wednesday.
He's not a 9-5'er.
He's a college student.
One without a set of wheels.
Both locations
are on this bus route.
And I found 3 sporting goods
store along that line.
Right.
Wait. Why do we care about
sporting goods all of a sudden?
Our student's a hiker. An ambitious one
if he got up to where the crash happened.
That's way off trail.
He'd need some serious gear
to get up there.
Come on. Let's go shopping.
Jaden: Blacksburg
is in Virginia.
Yeah. But the date on that ticket
stub is after the plane crash.
You said the plane crash didn't matter anyway.
I'm telling you...
no, we don't. We need to finish
to finish this profile before...
Michael.
What are you doing?
Alex here seems to
have it all figured out.
Well...
There's a lot of evidence that points to
Virginia as either the target location
or the meeting place between our
terrorist and the munitions expert.
Continue.
This is a ticket stub
to a theater in Blacksburg.
3:15 matinee of
"Elmo: The movie."
So far, our terrorist is
female, college-educated,
no kids, based in Brooklyn.
Driving all the way to Virginia to
see an Elmo movie is way weird.
So, that's where they met?
Maybe.
Definitely.
This is one of those
theaters with assigned seats.
Row G, seat 12.
And this is a stub G-11...
the person sitting next to her.
We know exactly
where they were sitting.
On Sunday the 10th
between 3:15 and 5:00 pm.
That's not bad.
We're after 100% confirmation.
If there are cameras,
you can get it.
What do you mean?
Tell him what you told me.
Hey, what's she doing in here?
Operations is off-limits
to recruits.
Go on.
Ok. I used to have
this friend Zeke,
and he used to bootleg DVDs
until they started putting
night vision cameras
inside the movie theaters.
Lyric theater
in Blacksburg, Virginia.
Think we can access
their security footage?
Who do you think
you're talking to?
10th. 3:15 showing
in auditorium 4.
"Elmo: The movie"?
This is creepy.
G 11, G 12.
A, b, c...
get closer in on that couple.
Hey.
There's our reporter.
Reporter? I thought you said
this was an inactive mission.
And that must be her source.
Just for training.
How long before facial recognition can
pinpoint the name of the new guy?
Don't need it. Dude used his credit
card to buy that tub of popcorn.
Benjamin Prentice.
North Virginia state.
Member of the outdoors club.
Great. Get me
his home address.
Gold star.
Wait. I wanna
go on the mission.
Maybe next time.
Why don't you stay
here with Birkhoff
and observe from operations?
You've earned it.
Ok, Michael. You are 5 miles
from destination.
Head east in 400 feet.
Or don't. Whatever.
Michael: Copy that.
Pretty cool how you can hack
into all these servers.
Local theaters.
Local police.
FBI?
It's called ownage, girl.
I don't have to hack Jack.
All these systems are already hacked.
I own them.
One button. Boom.
"Sneakers." River Phoenix.
Rent it. What's up?
Division's lucky to have you.
Tell that to Percy
and the dragon queen.
They thought I was a mole.
Fascists.
[Doorbell rings]
Nikita: Ben!
Prentice!
Ok. Please! Please!
Don't hurt me.
Ok. Prentice.
Don't be a wuss.
Nobody gets hurt.
We just want to see the video.
It's gone. I trashed it right
after I saw you kill that guy.
I didn't kill anybody.
Ben, we know you have it.
And if we have to waste time
looking for it,
the real killers...
the ones in the video...
they're gonna show up.
How are they going to find me?
The manager at ace sporting
goods... your buddy...
he was really helpful. He'd thought
you'd enjoy a visit from 2 hot babes.
It's going to be a lot easier
for the black helicopter guys
unless we get that video
out in the open.
What's it gonna be?
[Helicopter whirring]
Ben, on video: The plane crashed.
The plane crashed.
There's so much fire.
Wait.
Oh, my...
They're all...
they're all dead.
What?
It's gotta be 4 metric
tons of product there.
They must have overweighted
the plane.
Oh, sh...
Let's get this uploaded.
What's the paper's address?
Guardianpost.com.
Wi-fi's jammed.
What's going on?
I'm calling the cops.
You're gonna bring
the cops here?
I need your cell phone. Now!
I thought you told me that
they control the police.
They control information flow,
not trigger fingers.
Locals will come,
they'll arrest you,
they'll take you in.
You'll be safe for a couple of hours.
Come on!
A couple of hours?
Trust me. Ok.
There's no bars.
They're jamming everything.
Phone lines are down.
All other communication is jammed.
All right, listen up.
Our we level's 4.
Silencer's on.
No need to wake the neighbors.
Are those the feds?
Get away from there.
Don't go out there.
They're in there!
[Silenced gunshots]
Get down!
Ahh!
[Sirens approaching]
[Tires squealing]
Copy the video onto
your flash drive now.
[Police radio chatter]
Where the hell
did they come from?
I don't know.
Ugh, red bull.
Ahh.
Birkhoff, I thought you said
the satellites were down?
Birkhoff?!
Michael, sats are down.
Chill.
Then how'd the cops get here?
I don't know.
[Typing]
The cops got a dispatch.
I don't know where from.
White female.
Yadda, yadda, yadda.
It's just a local pd
looking for the reporter.
Nikita's in the house.
They have no idea.
Tell the cops
you're coming out.
Arms and hands in the air.
What about you?
The commando boys will be
forced to split their teams.
Send a unit to follow the cops.
They'll have less guys to attack me with.
Don't worry.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Jill...
Tell 'em your story.
I'm counting on you.
Man: Walk slowly toward us,
Ms. Morelli.
Keep your hands up.
Second man: Hands behind your back.
Turn around.
All right, clear the house.
Mobile one,
follow the reporter.
Mobile two will stay with me.
It's clear.
We're good to go.
Locals have cleared the house.
Think Nikita's still in there?
Yeah.
Nikita?
We found your wireless bug.
It was pretty clever.
Ol' birkhoff had no idea.
Nikita: Not such
a smart guy after all.
Does birkhoff have a toothache
or did Percy just cancel him?
No, he's alive.
But it could have
gone either way.
You put him in danger, Nikita.
That's not like you.
You don't know me anymore,
Michael.
Drop it. Drop it.
Don't!
Drop it.
Nikita.
Tell your man to drop it
or I drop him.
She won't hurt me.
Shut up!
Get down!
This isn't going to work.
Ahh!
Look.
The more you try to do this,
the more you hurt yourself.
Michael.
You have no idea how
much pain I can take.
[Groans]
What's this?
Cd player.
They used to have them,
you know, before mp3s.
Shut up.
Division won't let us have
anything with a hard drive.
Wait, so...
you succeed, you get rewarded.
Jaden took the TV for her room,
but I figure, you know,
she's been here longer,
so whatever.
Here.
["Tornado" by Jons playing]
I can't remember
the last time I heard music.
You deserve it, Alex.
[Clears throat]
She got away.
The, um, terrorist.
It was an active mission.
She got away.
Yeah, I heard.
That's not our fault.
We did our jobs.
Female reporter: With
Henry Sampson's arrest,
air America's stock
has continued to plummet,
losing nearly 70% of
its market value overnight.
Sampson was allegedly in cahoots
with the Vargus cartel,
coordinating over
a dozen cocaine shipments
between Colombia
and the United States.
The suspected cartel members
in the notorious video
released by "The Post"
remain at large.
You'll
I wonder if I'm allowed
ever to see
to ever be free
I wonder if I'm allowed
just ever to be
Oh!
Pepper spray.
Hey, you can never be
too careful.
How's the new gig?
Pretty great, actually.
Breaking a national story of a drug
running airline made me kinda popular.
Jill, you have to stop
digging into this.
Digging into what?
You know what?
No, you know.
And you won't even
give me their name.
You're only breathing because
you don't know their name.
And because killing the journalist
who took down air America
would make people look further
into Jeremy Holt's murder.
What gets me is, Jeremy's family
will never know the truth.
And that these people,
whoever they are,
they get away with it.
And no one can stop them.
I'm going to stop them.
Well, see you don't have
to do it alone.
I can help.
I'm not alone, Jill.
But if I need your help,
I'll ask.
I promise.
Can I quote you on that?
Not really.
[Rewinding]
"But if I need your help,
I'll ask."
Oh, wait!
Corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net